General
Marist Archives and Special Collections
General
2.1.1.1.13.1
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1192
- General, 2.1.1.1.13.1
  - Sunrise over Vesuvius in the Bay of Naples, circa 1909; 18; 8000; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Sunrise over the Bay of Naples, circa 1909; 19; 8001; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Sunrise over Vesuvius, circa 1909; 20; 8002; 1167; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Head sea, Caronia, circa 1909; 21; 8004; 4x5 film (Box 1192)
  - Heavy head sea, Caronia, circa 1909; 22; 8005; 4x5 film (Box 1192)
  - Sunset, circa 1909; 23; 8006; 1302; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Spray from head sea on Caronia, circa 1909; 24; 8007; 1305; 4x5 film (Box 1192)
  - Spray from head sea on Caronia, circa 1909; 25; 8008; 1304; 4x5 film (Box 1192)
  - Sunset, circa 1909; 26; 8009; 1300; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Sunset at sea, circa 1909; 27; 8010; 1299; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Sunset, circa 1909; 28; 8013; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Sunset and ships, circa 1909; 29; 8014; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Sunset, circa 1909; 30; 8015; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Sunset picture, circa 1909; 31; 8016; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Sunset picture, circa 1909; 32; 8018; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Sunset picture, circa 1909; 33; 8019; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Boys at Genoa, circa 1909; 34; 8020; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Shipping at Genoa, circa 1909; 35; 8021; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Vesuvius, Naples, circa 1909; 36; 8026; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Eruption of Vesuvius 1905 (copy), 1909 February; 37; 9; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Vesuvius in eruption (copy), 1909 February; 38; 10; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Victor Emmanuel, King of Italy (copy), circa 1909; 39; 8029; 1253; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Limone, Lago di Garda, copy, 1910 July; 40; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Riva, Lago di Garda, copy, 1910 July; 41; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Malcesine, Lago di Garda, copy, 1910 July; 42; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Riva, Vista dalla Strada del Ponale, copy, 1910 July; 43; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Riva sur Garda, copy, 1910 July; 44; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Lago di Loppio, copy, 1910 July; 45; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Isola di Garda, copy, 1910 July; 46; 4x5 (Box 1192)
  - Display of skulls, copy, 1910 July; 47; 4x5 (Box 1192)